喂?
Hello?
你长什么样?
What do you look like?
大声点
Talk louder!
我听不到
I can't hear you!
嘿,喂!
Hey, hello!
喂!我听不到你说话
Hello! I can't hear you!
5个
Five.
不知道
I don't know.
我不知道
让她精神集中点! 我来了
Get her in focus! Here I come!
开门,糟了
Open up! Shit!
上帝啊,你怎么--?
Jesus H. Christ!
What are you--?
怎么了?
What happened?
现在他有压力了,他拿到了球
Now he's got pressure.
He has a receiver!
当需要放松时
When it's time to relax
一罐啤酒足矣
One beer stands clear
哦,该死的
Oh, damn it!
特悌?
Tweety?
哦,该死,特悌,你就不能再等一个教学日吗?
Oh, shit, Tweety! Couldn't you
have waited for a school day?
请不要
Won't you please
Please won't you be
这家伙是谁?
Who the hell is this guy?
发生什么了?
What the hell's going on?
富勒里, 怎么回事?
Freeling, what's goin' on here?
我道歉
我邻居也是同一个频段
I apologize!
My neighbor's on the same remote!
我为这场比赛连命都赌上了,你开玩笑吧
I bet my life on this game!
Are you kiddin' me?
本,我们那正在放一场精彩的球赛
Hi, Ben. We got a good
football game goin' on here.
我的孩子要看"罗杰先生"
My kids wanna watch
"Mr. Rogers."
我不在乎你要看什么,你就算是可怜可怜我们
I don't care what you're watchin'!
Just show some mercy with that thing!
别啊,史迪夫
Come on, Steve!
把你的遥控器拿开
Move your set.
- 拿开,本
- 就这样,别换了
- Move yours, Ben.
- There it is. Don't move.
特悌不喜欢这个味道
Tweety doesn't like that smell.
甜心,特悌闻不到什么味道
Sweetheart,
Tweety can't smell a thing.
给他献朵花吧
Put a flower with him.
一朵花?
A flower?
为了他生气的时候
For when he's hungry.
为了他不再孤单
For when he's lonely.
为了他将度过的长夜.
For when it's nighttime.
没事了
Oh, it's okay.
现在我躺下长眠...
Now I lay me down to sleep...
我祈祷主宽恕我的灵魂
I pray the Lord my soul to keep.
- 哦,天哪
- 忍着点
- Oh, brother.
- Stifle it.
如果我在醒来之际死去...
If I should die before I wake...
会的
It did.
我请求主带走我的灵魂
I pray the Lord my soul to take.
你这样很可爱,很可爱
That was lovely.
Lovely, honey.
妈,等尸体腐烂之后能把骨头挖出来吗?
Mom, when it rots,
can we dig up the bones?
罗比,你就不能从树上下来?
Robbie! Will you come
on down out of the tree?
E. Buzz!
我们现在能养条金鱼了吗
Can I have a goldfish now?
来吃啊
Come and get it.
你把他们喂的太饱了
You're overfeeding them.
二十二和二十三还想要
Tweety Two and Tweety Three
want seconds.
你知道怎么回事吗,你喂的太多了?
You know what happens
when you overfeed goldfish?
他们要长成...鲨鱼
They grow up to be... sharks!
晚安
Good night.
妈妈.有大风暴要来了
Mom, there's a big storm
headed this way.
如果你们快点
风暴在你们入睡之后才会来
You'll be asleep by the time
it gets here if you hurry.
来,到被子里去
Come on. In you go.
晚安,宝贝
Good night, sweetie.
好,关灯了
Okay, lights out.
灯灭了!
Closet light!
我的错
My fault.
开灯,妈妈
Turn it on, Mommy!
够了吧?
That enough?
- 行吧?
- 晚安,妈
- Okay?
- Good night, Mom.
晚安.妈妈
Night, Mommy.
晚安
Good night.
我死了或是疯了
Either I'm dead or I'm crazy.
皮特,你没有疯
You're not crazy, Pete.
那你是说我死了?
You mean I'm dead?
我--
I'm--
你是说--
你是说这是好事?
You mean--
You mean this is for good?
梦游啊
Sleepwalking.
晚上的梦游症,你不知道吗?
Nocturnal somnambulism.
You know what?
我跟你打赌,这是遗传的
I will bet you anything
it's genetic.
卡罗尔昨晚就是,整个星期的晚上都在梦游
I mean, Carol Anne last night
and all last week.
我十岁的时候也是
And me when I was ten.
- 你能搞定这个吗?
- 好
- Would you deal with this?
- Sure.
你知道..
You know...
一次我梦游外出...
once I slept-walked four blocks...
在一个伙计的车的后座上睡着了
and I fell asleep
in the back of this guy's car.
你一直开着车,去工作也没发现我
He drove all the way to work
before discovering me.
天,然后我醒来了,开始狂叫
God, I woke up,
I started screaming.
人们跑过来,叫了警察
People came running, called the cops.
警察把这个可怜的花花公子带到市区
The cops took
this poor dude downtown.
- 我父亲, Ed--
-Big.
- My father, Ed--
- Big.
Big Ed 还检查了我有没有受伤,
有没有被侮辱
Big Ed has me examined
for bruises and hickeys.
天啊,真是太尴尬了
God, I was so embarrassed!
哦,天,史迪夫
Oh, shit, Steve.
如果我们挖个水池.你知道...
What if we dig the pool,
you know...
在没有水之前,卡罗尔梦游时掉进去了会怎么样?
and Carol Anne sleepwalks and falls
into it before there's any water?
哦,亲爱的,别这样
Oh, honey, no.
甜心,你滑过3米长的滑板吗?
Have you ever dove off
a three-meter board, sweetheart?
- 三米是多少?
- 十英尺
- What's three meters?
- It's about ten feet.
我们把水池挖的离屋子近点
这样孩子们就可以从屋顶上跳下去了
Let's dig the pool closer to the house
and let the kids jump off the roof.
别,亲爱的
No, honey, honey, honey.
甜心,3米长的滑板就像个空气袋
A three-meter board is like
an air pocket, sweetheart.
当你跳水时就像自由落体一样?
When you dive off,
it's like free-falling, okay?
你要站好位置,3米远
You gotta get your feet in position.
Three meters.
亲爱的,你的跳水生涯已经结束了
Honey, your diving days are over.
我们在谈论奥林匹克,达尼,知道吧
We're talkin' Olympics,
Diane, okay?
让我看看你的起跳位置
Let me see your tuck position.
我们像天鹅一样展开
We can jackknife into the swan.
收缩,转身...
Twist, turn...
然后跳出去
and splash!
亲爱的,去鹦鹉螺号是对的
Honey, it's right to
the Nautilus machine.
看这个,收缩,伸展
Look at this, honey.
Before, after.
收缩,伸展
- 别了
- 我爱你
- Don't.
- I love you.
天,我喜欢你说脏话的样子
Oh, God, I love it
when you talk dirty!
风暴越来越近了
Storm is coming closer.
嘿, 搭档.
Hey, partner.
嘿,亲爱的
Hi, honey.
一切还好吧?
Is everything okay?
在打雷
It's thundering.
来,起来
Come on. Hop up.
你是风,我是风中的羽毛
跟妈妈说晚安
I'm the wind and you're the feather.
Say good night to Mom.
- 晚安.妈妈
- 晚安,宝贝
- Good night, Mom.
- Good night, sweetheart.
走咯
Here we go.
我不喜欢那根树
I don't like the tree, Dad.
那是根老树了,在这很久了
That's an old tree.
It's been around here a long time.
在我的朋友成为邻居前就在这
It was here before my company
built the neighborhood.
我不喜欢它的手臂
I don't like its arms.
- 它知道我住在这里,是吧?
- 它知道我们的一切
- It knows I live here, doesn't it?
- It knows everything about us.
那就是我在它旁边建房子的缘故,
它能保护我们
That's why I built the house next to it,
so it could protect us.
你,卡罗尔,达纳,你妈妈和我
You and Carol Anne
and Dana and your mom and me.
这是根老而智慧的树
It's a very wise old tree.
它看着我,它知道我在这
It looks at me.
It knows I live here.
我想,风暴会掠过我们而去
I think the storm's gonna pass us.
你怎么知道的?
How do you know?
我能算出
'Cause I can count.
你知道怎么做?
You know what you do?
看到闪电时...
When you see the lightning...
就开始数,知道听到雷声
you count 'til you hear the thunder.
如果数的多说明风暴远了
If you can count higher each time,
that means the storm's movin' away.
想试试吗?
Wanna try it?
需要一些闪电啊
We need some lightning.
等等,来了
Wait. It's comin'.
好,开始数,1,2,3
Okay, count.
One, two, three.
跟你打赌,下次肯定可以数到4或者5
Next time, you'll be able to count
to at least four or five. Bet you.
爸,找你的
Daddy, it's for you.
让他们留个信,亲爱的
Tell them to take
a message, sweet pea.
我爸让你们留话
My dad wants to take a message.
晚安
Night.
太热了
It's too hot.
好,晚安,小天使
Okay. Night, angel.
- 做个好梦,好吗?
- 晚安,爸
- Happy dreams, okay?
- Night, Daddy.
1...
One...
2...
two...
3--
three--
我没有.少来了
I did not. Come on!
- 晚安,达尼
- 晚安.爸
- Good night, Dana.
- Good night, Dad.
- 别打电话了,达尼
- 好的,爸
- Get off the phone, Dana.
- Okay, Dad.
1...
One...
2--
two--
3...
Three...
4--
four--
5--
Five--
他们来了
They're here.
听我说,杰夫
不,我不开玩笑
Listen to me, Jeff.
No, I'm not kidding.
我知道,但谁在6.5级的风暴中还睡的着呢?
I know. How could anybody
sleep through a 6.5?
卧室受到损害,碎片到处都是
There was damage. Yeah, the bedroom.
There's stuff in pieces all over.
我们在听收音机,但是什么都没有
We're listening to the radio.
There's nothing on the radio at all.
你真讨厌,让我疯了
You are so obnoxious!
You drive me nuts!
力场
Force field.
- 你真讨厌
- 击中我的鼻子了
- You are so obnoxious.
- Got my nose.
这意味着战争,我也这么认为
This means war, and I mean it!
- 嘿,看着点
- 宝贝,你应该把食物咀嚼10次
- Hey, watch out.
- Honey, chew your food ten times.
你像个呕吐袋
You're a big barf bag.
你才像
You're a doggie bag.
- 我不吃了
- 你要吃的
- I won't eat it.
- There you go.
甜心,昨晚你说 ''他们来了''之时--
Sweetheart, last night
when you said, "They're here"--
我能把金鱼带到学校去吗?
Can I take my goldfish to school?
也许出问题的地方正好在房子下
但那些不用发出尖叫声吧?
Maybe the fault line runs directly under
our house. Wouldn't that be a scream?
天花板一直在我床头响
The ceiling got crumbs
all over my bed.
记得你昨晚醒来说"他们来了"吗?
Remember last night when you woke up
and said, "They're here"?
你说谁呢,谁来了?
Who did you mean?
Who's here?
电视里的人
The TV people.
- 她醉了
- 你怎么知道?
- She's stoned.
- What do you know?
比你强! 问爸爸吧!
More than you! Ask Dad!
- ''问爸爸吧''
- ''问爸爸吧!''
- "Ask Dad!"
''问爸爸吧!''
"Ask Dad!"
不是我的错
It's not my mess!
真是太感谢你,笨蛋,20分钟后我要去上学
Thanks a lot, jerko.
I've got class in 20 minutes.
自责之前把这交给我处理吧
Give me this
before you cut yourself.
地球是为你而运转的吗?
Did the earth move for you?
杰夫,这对我们来说不是同样的事情?
It wasn't quite the same
thing for us, Jeff. Huh?
好,对,就是的
Okay. Yeah, right. Okay.
- 我来处理这些
- 不是我的错
- Give me that before you cut yourself.
- It's not my fault.
再见,我走了
Bye, sweet pea.
I'm outta here.
- 再见,甜心
- 我也走了.
- Bye, honey.
- I'm outta here.
- 我可以送你
- 我去学校了
- You I can handle.
- I got school.
- 好,先吃早餐
- 好,那我就不及格了
- Well, breakfast first.
- All right. I'll just flunk.
每种工作都会有意外发生
It happens on every job.
看这个
Look at this!
我喜欢那小妞
I love that swing.
我爱你,我爱你
I love you. I love you.
我喜欢
I love it.
E. Buzz, 不不,
下来
E. Buzz, no, no!
Get down.
卡罗尔,我叫你们吃完后把椅子放进去的
Carol Anne, I've told you guys
to push your chairs in when you're done.
你会毁了你的眼睛的,这样不好
Honey, you're gonna ruin your eyes.
This is not good for you.
怎么了啊?
What's the matter?
你干什么?
What are you doing?
- 如何?
- 很棒, 富勒里女士.
- How is it?
- Great, Mrs. Freeling.
- 好,布努托,把杯子给我
- 你的咖啡不错
- Okay, Bluto, give me my cup.
- You sure make good coffee.
天,别那样
Oh, Jesus!
Don't do that, honey.
你想把妈妈吓死吗?
You wanna see Mommy lying in a cigar box
covered with licorice?
是你做的?
Did you do this?
你们啊
You guys.
我叫你们别把椅子拉出来
I asked you
not to pull the chairs out.
电视人?
The TV people?
你看见他们了?
Do you see them?
有吗?
Do you?
我想你们肯定会很喜欢这个厨房的
I think you're really
gonna enjoy this kitchen.
最新装修过,我们管这叫第四代
This is our latest development.
We call this phase four.
你住哪?, 富勒里先生?
Where do you live, Mr. Freeling?
我们是第一批住到佛得角山脉的人
We were the first family to set up house
in the Cuesta Verde Estates.
第一代
Oh, phase one.
我要穿过邻居的房子才能到这
We had to pass through
my neighborhood to get here.
那块有圣灵的地方
Oh, that area with
the lived-in look.
是有那么个说法,但是很快就不能分辨...
It has that, but in a couple of months
you won't be able to distinguish...
第一代,第二代和第三代了--
phase one from phase three to phase--
我们这有句谚语
We have a saying around here.
''草在每边都长的更绿.''
"The grass grows greener
on every side."
- 那就是我摸索出来的
- 我分不清这些房子
- That's the way I feel about it.
- I can't tell one house from the other.
我想你是对的
I think you're right.
但是我觉得我们的建筑标准还是很宽大的
But I think our construction standards
are really very liberal.
我有个邻居,他在自家的浴室里按了个
极可意牌浴缸...
I have this neighbor, and he built
his Jacuzzi in his bedroom...
它的出水管连在外面的浅水池
and it has a running aqueduct
connected to a wading pool outside.
一半在屋子里,一半在外面
It's built half in
and half out of his living room.
还上了昨日"城市与乡村"的封页
It was featured in last month's
issue of "Town and Country."
我带你去看看
I'll show you the den.
甜心,过来,快
Honey, come here, quick!
-快带你,在停止之前
- 但是这些罐子--
- Hurry, before it stops again!
- But the cans--
- 放松
- 好
- Easy.
- All right.
站这吧?
Just stand right here, okay?
我没让达纳和罗比知道,但是卡罗尔在这
所以她看见了
I've kept Dana and Robbie out of this,
but Carol Anne was here so she knows.
达纳不会保密,而罗比肯定要吓死
Dana would blab, and Robbie
would be up for three weeks.
我想你应该坐下
I think you should sit down.
就站着,行吗?
Now just stand, okay?
现在冷静下来
Now just be calm.
当你放开思维时想想我们的过去
Now reach back into our past
when you used to have an open mind.
记得吧?
Remember that?
下几分钟都要那么想
Just try to use that
for the next couple of minutes.
- 好吗?
- 好
- Okay?
- Okay.
妈妈没给做晚餐
Mother didn't cook any dinner.
我们去吃比萨吧?
We'll go to Pizza Hut, okay?
看着
Now just look.
只要看着
Just look. Just watch.
过来,宝贝
Come here, sweetheart.
你能把椅子移开...
Honey, could you move
the chair out of the way...
然后坐在那行吗?
and just stay down there?
- 让爸爸看看
- 我饿了
- Let's show Daddy.
- I'm hungry.
别跟妈妈争了
Now don't argue with Mommy.
我们再做一遍
Let's just do this once.
好,开始了
Okay, here we go.
我想要意大利香肠比萨
I want pepperoni pizza.
妈妈,热
Mommy, that burns.
地板还要打点腊,史迪夫,你来
The floor needs more wax.
Steven, you do it.
宝贝,试试
Honey, try.
好像有种回旋力...
It's like there's this tickling...
就在这,开始拉你
right in here,
and it starts to pull you.
然后就好像突然没有了空气...
It pulls you, and suddenly
it's like there's no air...
除非你能呼吸,
然后你开始感觉被拉下来--
except that you can breathe,
and you're getting pulled along--
- 嘿 本.
- 杜希尔先生, 嘿
- Hi, Ben.
- Mr. Tuthill, hi.
我的电视没开,所以如果你的遥控器有什么问题--
My TV's not on, so if you're
havin' problems with your set--
不是这个
戴安和我想知道--
It's nothing like that.
Diane and I were just wondering--
-这听起来比较荒唐
-我也不相信
-This will sound strange coming from me.
-I doubt that.
蚊子太恐怖了
The mosquitoes are awful.
它们真该死
They're chowin' down.
它们从不来烦我
I've never been bothered by 'em.
我觉得自己没被咬过
I don't think I've ever
been bitten by one of 'em.
据我所知,我们家还没被咬过
As far as I know, nobody in my family's
ever been affected by 'em.
蚊子从没咬过你,是吧儿子?
Mosquito ever suck on you, son?
- 我不知道,爸爸
- 他不知道
- I don't know, Dad.
- He don't know.
看
Look.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
嗯, 杜希尔先生,看
Uh, Mr. Tuthill, look.
我们只是--
我们想知道的是--
We were just--
What we were wondering--
戴安,我的妻子,
和我想知道,本...
Diane, my wife,
and I were wondering, Ben...
隔壁有些有趣的事情发生
somethin' funny's
goin' on here next door.
有些--
Somethin', uh--
我们想知道你们最近有没有被什么东西骚扰
We were wondering if maybe you had
experienced any disturbances lately.
什么骚扰?
What kind of disturbances?
你知道...
Um, oh, you know, like...
像盘子啊家具啊自己移动
dishes or furniture
moving around by themselves.
别抓,会影响痊愈的
Don't scratch.
You're gonna infect 'em.
让我给你涂上
Just let me put this on.
- 别
- 我像个傻瓜
- Don't.
- Boy, did I feel like a fool.
抱歉,但是得涂上,我想有点失血
I'm sorry, but I had to say something.
We were losing blood.
- 这事儿还得出现在我们家
- 别抓
- We'll keep this thing in the family.
- Don't scratch.
明天我去叫几个人
Tomorrow I'll call somebody.
比如,谁呢?
我已经看过黄页了
Who, for instance?
I already looked in the Yellow Pages.
给我们搬家具得人
真奇怪,也没有清单
Furniture movers we got.
Strange phenomena, there's no listing.
1,1千,2,2千...
One, one thousand,
two, one thousand...
3,3千,4,4千...
three, one thousand,
four, one thousand...
5,5千--
five, one thousand--
看
Honey, look.
我天天遇到这种变态的事情但是也没什么坏处
I lived with this freaky thing all day
and nothing bad happened.
这好像就是大自然的另一方面,
一个我们没资格了解的方面
It's like another side of nature, a side
that we're not qualified to understand.
当你过度反映,那么发生的就很重要
When you overreact, it makes
what happened much too important.
我知道发生了什么之前不准进厨房
No one's goin' in the kitchen
'til I know what's happening.
1,1千,2,2千...
One, one thousand,
two, one thousand...
3,3千,--
three, one thousand,
four, one thousand--
1,1千,2,1千,3---
One, one thousand,
two, one thousand, three--
1,1千,2,2千.--
One, one thousand,
two, one thousand--
救命
Help me!
- 救我,爸爸
- 小心
- Help me, Dad!
- Be careful!
爸,快点
Dad, come on!
救命
Help me!
他来了
He's coming!
它要吃下我了
It's taking me in!
- 他来了
- 它弄伤我了
- He's coming!
- It's hurting me!
- 史迪夫,快点
- 爸爸,快救我
- Steven, hurry!
- Dad, help me!
- 坚持住
- 抓住他
- Hold on!
- Hold on to him!
抓住我,爸爸!
Hold me, Dad!
- 抓住了
- 我的腿
- I got him!
- My leg!
爸爸,我的腿
Dad, my leg!
救命啊,爸爸
Help me, Dad!
看,爸妈,是龙卷风
Look, Mom, Dad!
It's a tornado!
它刚才肯定是忽略了我们
不会有一幢房子幸免的--
It must've just skimmed us.
There wouldn't be a house left if--
我把她留在了楼上
I left her upstairs!
宝贝,我们来了
Baby, we're coming!
- 我去查厨房
- 不,我去
- I'll go check the kitchen.
- No! I'll do it!
你检查自己的卧室
You check your room.
宝贝?
Baby?
甜心?
Sweetheart?
宝贝?
Baby?
找到她了?
Did you find her?
我哪都找了,真是疯了
I've looked everywhere.
This is crazy.
噢,我的天
Oh, my-- My God.
泳池
The swimming pool.
小心,亲爱的
Be careful, honey!
妈咪
Mommy!
没事
Nothing!
谢天谢地
Thank God.
什么?
What?
噢,卡罗尔,谢天谢地
Oh, Carol Anne, thank God! Baby!
宝贝,你在哪?
Baby, where are you?
- 妈咪.过来
- 什么?
- Mommy, come over here!
- What is it?
什么,宝贝?
What, baby?
妈妈,我听不到
I can't hear you, Mommy.
你在哪?
Where are you?
我听不到你,妈妈
I can't hear you, Mommy!
你在哪?
Where are you?
有哪些家庭成员被牵扯进去...
What members of the household
are involved...
他们都多大了?
and what are their ages?
有达尼,我的妻子,31岁
There's Diane, my wife.
She's 31.
啊,是32,对不起
Uh, 32. I'm sorry.
我最大的女儿,16岁
My oldest daughter, Dana.
She's 16.
我的儿子,罗伯特,8岁
My son, Robert, is eight.
5个
Five.
这件事公开过吗?
Has there been any publicity
about these events?
绝对没有
Absolutely nothing.
你敢确定...
Can you be reasonably sure...
没有理由让这些发生?
of not letting any get started?
这就是我们最后希望的
That's the last thing we want.
我们还没去过警察局呢
We haven't even gone to the police.
你的家庭会欢迎...
Would your family welcome...
一个对此事的严密调查吗...
a serious investigation
of these disturbances...
这项调查可以让他们掌握第一手资料?
by someone who can make
firsthand observations?
听着, 莱斯博士,
我们不在乎那些--
Look, Dr. Lesh,
we don't care about the disturbances--
打扰你们的的重击,...
the pounding and the flashing...
尖叫,音乐
the screaming, the music.
我们只要你们找到我的小女儿
We just want you
to find our little girl.
我想应该警告你们...
I guess I should warn you that...
我们把这间屋子锁起来跟其他房间隔开
we keep the room locked off
from the rest of the house.
罗比跟我们睡, 达纳多跟朋友呆着一起
Robbie's sleeping with us now, and Dana
spends a lot of time with friends.
这种事情一共发生过多少回?
How many disturbances
have you recorded in the room?
我们不进那个屋子了
We don't go in the room anymore.
富勒里先生,我们会记录下任何物理的能量
变化和力场波动
Mr. Freeling, we'll record
any psychotropic energy or event.
是, 赖安曾在红土地上拍下了
一起事件十分有趣的环节
Yes, Ryan photographed an extraordinary
episode on a case in Redlands.
是的,是一个小孩子的玩具,
一个火柴盒大小的交通工具
That's right. It was a child's toy,
a very small Matchbox vehicle.
它滚了7英尺,穿过了一张油布毯
It rolled seven feet
across a linoleum surface.
这持续了7个小时
The duration of the event
was seven hours.
怎么会7个小时?
Seven hours for what?
让它花时间完成这段距离
For the vehicle
to complete the distance.
当然,一般的肉眼难以相信...
Of course, this would never
register on the naked eye...
但是我用高速照相机拍下了
but I have it recorded
on time-lapse camera.
太奇妙了
It's fantastic.
我们一直努力维护这个家庭
We've been trying to
hold ourselves together as a family.
当然,大家现在睡的都很少
Of course,
no one's been sleeping much.
史迪夫也错过了那么多工作
Steven has missed so much work.
但是他确实很想知道这是什么原因
But he's been wonderful.
Really wonderful.
你调查闹鬼的房子有多久了?
How long have you been
investigating haunted houses?
- 富勒里女士--
- 戴安
- Mrs. Freeling--
- Diane.
下决定说你的屋子闹鬼还不是件很容易的事情
The determination as to whether
your home is haunted is not very easy.
我的意思是...
What I meant to say was...
可能是个恶作剧...
it might very well be
a poltergeist intrusion...
而不是所谓的闹鬼
instead of a classic haunting.
有区别吗?
There's a difference?
看见了吗?
Did you see that?
会有两次的,总是这样
There'll be two more.
They travel in pairs.
凯西博士.
Dr. Casey.
应该行动快点.
Gotta be quicker than that.
是电路原因,你可以闻到
It's electrical.
You can smell the charge.
是不是会闹恶作剧的鬼?
What about poltergeists?
闹恶作剧的鬼通常跟个人联系在一起的
Poltergeists are usually
associated with an individual.
闹鬼通常跟...
Haunting seem to be connected...
屋里一块区域有关
with an area,
a house, usually.
这种骚乱一般时间很短
Poltergeist disturbances
have a fairly short duration.
大概2个月
Perhaps a couple of months.
而闹鬼则可能持续几年
Haunting can go on for years.
你是说这些事情可以很快就结束?
Are you telling me that all of this
could just suddenly end at any time?
是的
Yes, it could.
除非这不是一般的闹鬼
Unless it's a haunting.
但是闹鬼一般不会跟活人扯上关系啊
But haunting don't usually
revolve around living people.
我们时间不多了,我女儿还活在这房子里
Then we don't have much time, because
my daughter is alive in this house.
她正在躲避莫名其妙的攻击
While trying to escape
from an unknown assailant.
马歇尔别确定病危得到严密的照顾
Marshall is listed as critical
and under intensive care.
这有点奇怪
This is probably
gonna seem a little strange.
这个频道听起来好些
We hear better on this channel.
别问我原因
Don't ask me why.
嗯...
Well...
我想我对她说几句话
I guess I'll call her.
是妈妈,甜心
It's Mommy, sweetheart.
我们想和你谈话
We wanna talk to you.
请回答我,宝贝
Please answer me, baby.
请回答我
Please answer me.
小乖乖,跟我说话啊
Please talk to me, bunny.
看看这狗
Look at the dog.
你和我们在一起吗?
Are you with us now?
你能跟爸爸打声招呼吗?
Can you say hello to Daddy?
嘿,爸爸
Hello, Daddy.
嘿,小宝贝
Hello, sweet pea.
是妈妈,甜心
It's Mommy, sweetheart.
喂,妈妈
Hello, Mommy.
喂,宝贝
Hello, baby.
你能看见我吗?
Can you see me?
你能看见妈妈吗?
Can you see Mommy?
妈妈,你在哪?
Mommy, where are you?
Where are you?
我们在家,宝贝
We're home, baby.
We're home.
- 你能找到回家的路,回到我们身边吗?
- 妈妈,你在哪?
- Can you find a way home to us, baby?
- Mommy, where are you?
我找不到你
I can't find you!
I can't!
我害怕灯光,妈妈
I'm afraid of the light, Mommy!
我怕光
I'm afraid of the light!
叫她离光远点
Tell her to stay away
from the light!
- 也许这是出来的路
- 也许是,但不是给她的
- Maybe it's a way out.
- It is, but not for her.
快告诉她
Tell her quickly.
- 离光远点
- 告诉她,戴安
- Stay away from the light!
- Tell her, Diane.
离光远点
Stay away from the light!
光很危险,别靠近
The light is dangerous!
Don't go near it!
- 甚至别看一眼
- 我不信
- Don't even look at the light!
- I don't believe it.
声音有可能是通过民用波段传过来的
The voice could be coming
from a CB transmitter.
这不是什么愚弄
This isn't a hoax!
那是什么?
What the hell is this?
是什么?
Anything?
- 什么都不敢确定
- 妈妈,这有人
- Nothing's registered.
- Mommy, there's somebody here.
是你吗?
Mommy, is that you?
不是妈妈
这是谁, 莱斯博士?
No, it's not Mommy.
Who is it, Dr. Lesh?
- 谁跟你在一起?
- Who's with you, baby?
- Who's with you?
有人来了,救我啊
Somebody's coming!
Help me, please!
我的天,我的孩子
My God! My baby!
你个混蛋,她只是孩子啊
You bastards!
She's just a baby!
救她,难道你没听出发生了什么?
Help her!
Can't you hear what's happening?
听
Listen!
别碰我,离我远点
Get away from me!
Leave me alone!
妈妈,救我啊
Mommy, help me!
她刚才穿过我了
She just moved through me.
天
My God!
我感觉到她了
I felt her.
我可以嗅到她
I can smell her!
是她
It's her!
闻我的衣服
她跟我同在
Smell my clothes.
She's all over me.
- 是她
- 我的天
- It's her.
- My God.
是她,我感觉到了
It's her. I felt her.
就是
It is. It's her.
It is.
是我的孩子
It's my baby.
她穿过了我的灵魂
She went through my soul.
我再也听不到她了?
I can't hear her anymore.
Honey?
当她从视线中消失的时候...
Where exactly do you suppose
Carol Anne was playing...
她是在哪玩的?
when she vanished from sight?
卡罗尔消失的时候在哪玩?
Where was Carol Anne playing
when she disappeared?
最靠近她的卧室
Her bedroom closet.
我们去哪
Let's go up there.
他们不让你进
They won't let you in.
我们要去看看
We'll just see about that.
你怎么啦?
Whatever happened to you?
我不知道-我只是去检查孩子的房间
I was just about to check out
the kid's bedroom when-- I don't know.
有东西咬了我一口
Something took a bite outta me.
你被咬了?
You got bit?
-世界上最恐怖的肌肉痉挛
-我看看
-That or the world's worst muscle spasm.
-Let's have a look.
-想想我们还是在楼下睡觉
-不,错了
-Think we'll spend the night downstairs.
-No. Wrong.
甜心,你带着孩子俩去镇里过夜
Honey, you take Dana and Robbie
and go and spend tonight in town.
我不离开卡罗尔
I am not leaving here
without Carol Anne.
爸妈,这我再也呆不下了
Mom, Dad, I can't stay here anymore.
好,宝贝,你们去
You go, baby, go.
我不会丢下这房子里的任何人的
I'm not gonna leave
anybody in this house alone.
能和你谈谈吗?
Can we talk to you?
走
Let's go.
- 这些东西动了吗?
- 能测到一些点离子
- Any movement from those things?
- There's been some ionization flux.
我想确定是不是因为潮湿导致结构的变化...
I'd like to make sure they're not caused
by humidity from structure leakage...
但我不去那查什么原因
but I'm not goin' up there
to find out.
这儿发生的事情已经超过正常范围了
We have got much more than the
paranormal episode taking place here.
这房子里的科学力量...
There is a measurable
physical science in this house...
已经远远超过我遇到过的那些奇怪现象
that goes far beyond the creaking doors
or cold spots I've experienced.
电视上的声音
它是从哪来的?
The voice on television.
Where is it coming from?
没有接受任何电视信号...
The absence of a signal on a channel
that is not receiving a broadcast...
意味着它可以从很多东西那接受到声音.比如短波
means that it can receive a lot of noise
from many things, like short waves.
太阳黑子波动
汽车的电火花
Solar disturbances,
car ignition sparkings.
外太空,或是地下
Outer space.
Or inner space.
但是如果有块区域可以让人同时在两地出现?
What if these people have an area
of bilocation in their own living room?
你什么意思?
What do you mean?
如果那就是出来的路...
If that is the way out...
那就是说这房子有进去的路
then maybe somewhere in this house
there's a way in.
别,开着吧
No, please.
Leave it on.
谢谢
Thanks.
你知道,当这么安静时...
You know,
when it's quiet like now...
我就知道从你们的角度该如何审视这些事情了
I can imagine how all of this
must look from your side.
我真的很困惑
I'm really embarrassed.
废话
Nonsense.
我应该是那个跟你们来这受到困惑的人
I'm the one who should be embarrassed
being here with you nice people.
超心理学不是你该学习的东西
Parapsychology isn't something
you master in.
已经有两个毕业证书...
There are no
certificates of graduation...
但却没有工作执照
no licenses to practice.
我是个专业心理学家
I am a professional psychologist.
我毕生都献给了这些鬼鬼祟祟的事情
I spend most of my time
engaged in this ghostly hobby.
这让我成了这个年龄段最难让人接受的女人
Which makes me the most irresponsible
woman of my age that I know.
你不用拿个杯子吗?
Would you like a glass for that?
不,谢谢
No, thank you.
你知道,你很搞笑
You know, you were very funny.
你的手抖的很厉害
Your hands were shaking
about a mile a minute.
还没结束
This isn't over.
我十分的恐惧
I'm absolutely terrified.
尽是些我们无法理解的事情
It's all the things
that we don't understand.
我感觉,那些猿人从原始森林走出来...
I feel like the protohuman,
coming out of the forest primeval...
第一会看见了月亮,向它仍石子
and seeing the moon for the first time
and throwing rocks at it.
如果我被杀了,我能回来...
If I got killed,
would I come back...
像我的女儿一样被陷在房子里吗?
and get stuck in the house
like my sister?
你妹妹没死
Your sister isn't dead, Robbie.
如果我被杀了...
If I got killed...
我能去看望她,告诉如何出来吗?
could I visit her
and show her how to get back here?
你可以系跟绳子在我身上,紧紧的拉住...
You could tie a rope around me
and hold it tight...
那么人们就可以拉住我们不让我们陷进去
then somebody could come and get us,
and we could live somewhere else.
有人相信...
Some people believe...
人死后灵魂会升入天堂
that when you die,
your soul goes to heaven.
外公死时...
When Grandpa was dead...
我在医院的病床上看着他...
I looked at him in the hospital bed
and I was watching...
但是我没有见到有东西从他身上升起来
but I didn't see anything
go up out of him.
罗比,他的灵魂是看不见的
His soul is invisible, Robbie.
You couldn't see it.
但是外公为什么不和卡罗尔一起出现在电视上呢?
But how come Grandpa isn't
on television with Carol Anne?
有人相信人死后...
Some people believe
that when people die...
有个非常棒的灯...
there's a wonderful light...
和太阳一样明亮...
as bright as the sun...
并且并不刺眼
but it doesn't hurt
to look into it.
你所想知道所有问题的所有答案...
All the answers to all the questions
that you ever want to know...
都在这灯里面
are inside that light.
而当你走向它，你就永远成了它的一部分
And when you walk to it,
you become a part of it forever.
然后，一些人死了...
And then, some people die...
但是他们自己并不知道
but they don't know
that they've gone.
他们以为他们自己还活着?
They think they're still alive?
是的，可能他们并不想死
Maybe they didn't want to die.
可能他们还没有准备好
Maybe they weren't ready.
可能他们还没活够...
Maybe they hadn't
lived fully yet...
或者他们已经活了很长时间，
但是他们还想继续活下去
or they'd lived a long time,
but they still wanted more life.
他们拒绝走向那个灯光...
They resist going into that light...
无论那个灯多需要他们
however hard the light wants them.
他们留在了附近...
They just hang around...
看电视，看着他们的朋友长大...
watch TV,
watch their friends grow up...
感到不开心和嫉妒
feeling unhappy and jealous.
那些感情很不好
Those feelings are bad.
他们感到受伤害了
They hurt.
然后...
And then...
那些人...
some people...
失去了前往灯光的道路...
just get lost
on the way to the light...
他们需要有人来引导他们
and they need someone
to guide them to it.
所以那些人生气了...
So some people get angry...
并乱扔东西，像我的卧室一样?
and throw things around,
like in my bedroom?
就像在学校
Just like in school.
一些小朋友对你很好...
Like, some kids are nice to you...
另一些对你刻薄
some kids are mean.
我有一次被3个小孩打了
I got beat up once
by three kids.
他们拿走了我的午饭钱
They took my lunch money.
可能他们被卡车撞了，现在正在楼上呢
Maybe they got hit by a truck,
and they're upstairs right now.
听着, 也许我们该睡觉了，好吗?
Listen, partner, maybe we oughta
get some shut-eye, okay?
你知道吗?
You know what?
当我们告诉奶奶今晚...
When we called Grandma tonight...
她很兴奋你打算去陪她...
she got really excited that
you're comin' to stay with her...
她打算好好接待你们
and she's plannin' all these
neat things for you guys to do.
我可以带E. Buzz和我一起去吗?
Can I take E. Buzz with me
when we go?
当然可以
Sure you can.
- 晚安，妈妈
- 晚安，亲爱的
- Good night, Mom.
- Good night, sweetie.
晚安，女士
Night, lady.
晚安，爸爸
Night, Dad.
晚安, 罗比.
Night, Rob.
我爱你
I love you.
晚安, 卡罗尔.
Good night, Carol Anne.
我想去找点吃的
I'm gonna go
get something to eat.
那是什么?
What is it?
回放一下
Roll it back.
我想我们应该已经录下来了
I think we got one.
I think it recorded.
是的，录下来了
Yes. It recorded.
看看他们所有人
Look at all of them.
那是我们的房子吗?
Is that our house?
那些人是谁?
Who are all those people?
他们是这样孤独，这样孤独
They're so alone. So alone.
他们从哪里来?
Where are they coming from?
我不知道
I don't know.
打电话给我，好吗?
Call me, okay?
这块宝石已经有一百多年的历史了
This cameo is over
a hundred years old.
是的，挺长时间了?
Yeah, some haul, huh?
而这块表只有几年的历史，而它不是你们的
And this watch is only
a few years old, and it's not yours.
嗯，我先走了
Well, I'm off.
我要带着这些东西和录像带去实验室
I'm taking these back to the lab
along with the tapes.
你知道，我不得不展示它们
I'm going to have to
display these, you know.
- 请不要再“60分钟”上面
- 或是“难以置信”
- Please, not on "60 Minutes."
- Or "That's Incredible!"
对不起
I'll get it. Excuse me.
我会把赖安留在这里陪你
I'm leaving Ryan here with you.
马蒂不会回来了
Marty won't be coming back.
我会回来的
I am coming back.
并且我会带回来一些有帮助的东西
And I'll bring some help.
不要担心
Try not to worry.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我们在办公室很想你
We've missed you
down at the office.
小伙子们很担心，所以我过来看看--
The boys have gotten worried,
so I took it upon myself to--
天啊，史迪夫, 你看上去很糟糕
你现在感到好点了吗?
Jesus, Steve, you look like shit.
Aren't you feeling any better?
我还是感到很虚弱，逖格先生
我感冒了，我起不来--
I'm still weak, Mr. Teague.
I've got the flu, I can't get up--
你这里看上去好像有线电视坏了
Looks like you got
some cable problems here.
是的，有线坏了几个星期了
Yeah. The cable's been off
for a couple of weeks.
我们应该查一查。
这个街区的其他用户也坏了吗?
We'll have to look into that.
The rest of the block dark too?
不，只是我们
No, just us.
你这里电路好像也有点问题
You got some electrical problems
as well here.
你把什么东西装这里了，300瓦的灯泡?
What have you got screwed in there,
a 300-watt bulb?
你怕遭贼，或是打算吸引...
You afraid of burglars,
or are you trying to attract...
在佛得角山脉的所有昆虫?
every insect in Cuesta Verde?
- 史迪夫, 你在这里开心吗?
- 是的，先生
- Steve, are you happy here?
- Yes, I am, sir.
恕我冒昧问这些问题...
Forgive me for asking
all these questions...
但我们不想失去我们最好的职员...
but we don't want to lose
the best rep we've ever had...
因为感冒或是其他问题
to the flu
or other opportunities.
看了你起居室里的所有软件...
Seeing all that software
in your living room...
使我怀疑，也许你已经
得出点什么东西了
makes me wonder, maybe you've
got something going on the side.
不，我只是在看 “普通机械学”
我有这嗜好
No, I just read "Popular Mechanics."
I got hobbies.
想兜兜风吗?
Feel like going
for a little ride?
我有点东西想给你看
I'd like to show you something.
哦，天啊! 对不起!
Oh, God! I'm sorry!
你的一个孩子是在这屋子
里生下来的，对吗?
One of your children
was born in your house, huh?
我理解她错过了很多学校
I understand that she's
missed a lot of school.
崔斯克的一个女儿也是在同一个护士班
One of Trask's daughters
is in the same nursery class.
她也感冒了，是吗?
She got the flu as well, huh?
是的，我们都感冒了
Yeah, we've all got
the same thing.
对不起
I'm sorry.
- 我没看到她
- 她就在附近
- I didn't see her.
- She's around.
我想，你不介意我问你个问题吧
I wonder if you'd mind
if I asked you a question.
你是不是打算离开佛得角山脉?
Are you thinking about
leaving Cuesta Verde?
为什么这世界上的所有人在这样
的一天都会有个问题？
How could anyone in the world
have a problem...
on a day like this?
这个位置放个落地窗不错吧?
How's that spot
for a bay window?
你住在这里的话是不错，但是...
It's pretty nice if you're
living up here, but...
对于山谷里来说...
not so great
down in the valley...
看到山上有人家，就不怎么好看了
Looking at homes
cutting into the hillside.
你不需要继续住在山谷里了
You don't have to live
in the valley anymore.
你说什么?
What are you saying?
我们将在我们现在站的地方开始5个阶段
We're starting phase five
right here where we're standing.
这里可以成为你的主卧室套间
All of this can be
your master bedroom suite.
那里可以成为你的观景台，
有兴趣吗?
That can be your view.
Interested?
嗯，逖格先生，你真大方阿
Well, Mr. Teague,
that's a generous offer.
- 我不是个开发商
- 你负责 42% 的销售
- I'm just not a developer.
- You're responsible for 42o/o of sales.
那几乎是下面所有的一半了
That's almost half
of everything down there.
几乎是价值7千万美元的房产
Almost $70 million worth
of dwelling and properties.
那是一整套安全的发展计划...
That's a whole generation
of security...
没人可以往上面贴价格标签
that nobody
can put a price tag on.
我认为我们应该3年前就使你
成为我们的完全合伙人
I know we should have made you
a full partner three years ago.
我现在不想失去你
I don't want to lose you now.
这里没有空间造个游泳池吧?
Not much room
for a pool, is there?
我们有整块土地
We own all the land.
我们已经有了重新安排墓地的协议
We've already made arrangements
for relocating the cemetery.
你在开玩笑吧
You're kidding me.
- 这会遭天遣的，不是吗?
- 哦，不要担心
- That's sacrilegious, isn't it?
- Oh, don't worry about it.
毕竟，这不是古代部落的墓场
After all, it's not ancient
tribal burial ground.
这只是...人
It's just... people.
另外，我们以前也做过
Besides, we've done it before.
什么时候?
When?
76年，就在山谷里
In '76. Right down there.
佛得角山脉?
Cuesta Verde?
总共300亩土地，挺大的生意
All 300 acres.
It was quite a deal.
我从没听说过
But I never heard
anything about it.
这又不值得在广告牌上登广告...
It's not something
one advertises on a billboard...
或是登在汽车上
or on the side of a bus.
不要担心，朋友和亲属可以
在布朗斯顿公墓看望故去的人
Don't worry. Friends and relatives
can visit their loved ones...
in Broxton Memorial Park.
只有5分钟的路程
It's only five minutes further.
哦，是的，5分钟路程，不太远
Oh, yeah. Five minutes.
That's no great hardship.
我想应该没问题
I suppose that would be okay.
谁没问题?
Okay with whom?
可能会抱怨的人
Whomever might complain.
现在为止都没人抱怨
Nobody's complained until now.
我们在厨房有两种经历，这里是房间
We've had two experiences
in the kitchen. This is the den.
你们不要跟过来好吗?
Y'all mind hangin' back?
你们会干扰我的频率
You're jammin' my frequencies.
那么... 我们今晚研究彩虹的
哪一边, 莱斯博士?
So... what side of the rainbow
are we working tonight, Dr. Lesh?
- 这就是你的解决方案?
- 我知道你在想什么
- This your Knott's Berry Farm solution?
- I know what you're thinking.
但是你要记住我的话，她已经
驱清了很多屋子的鬼
But you must take my word for it.
She's cleaned many houses.
她的能力有所记载--
Her gifts have been documented--
那晚以后，我们没再听见过卡罗尔
We haven't heard Carol Anne
since last night.
这门为什么锁了，富勒里先生?
Why is this door locked,
Mr. Freeling?
- 回答她, 史迪夫.
- 我会的
- Answer her, Steven.
- I am.
我是说那个起居室
I am addressing the living.
对不起
I'm sorry.
那个房间是我的儿子和女儿住的
That's the room
my son and daughter used to occupy.
我们相信那是这个屋子的心脏
We believe it's the heart
of the house.
这个屋子有很多心脏
This house has many hearts.
- 怎么啦?
- What is the matter?
- What's the matter?
我试图用我的意念来回答她...
I was trying to answer her
with my mind...
但她听不见我
and she couldn't hear me.
我记得你说过坦基纳 柏恩
具有透视能力
I thought you said this Tangina Barrons
was an extraordinary clairvoyant.
我是有
I am.
我只是不喜欢欺骗性的答案
I just don't like trick answers.
过来，亲爱的...
Come here, honey...
把你的手给我
and give me your hand.
我不会伤到你的
I'm not gonna bite you.
低下来点，让我能够俯视你
Come on down here. You'll give me
a whiplash lookin' up at you.
你女儿还活在这间屋子里
Your daughter is alive
and in this house.
最后一次事件发生在哪里?
Where was the last incident
of bilocation?
我强烈感觉到...
I get my strongest feelin'...
源头起于孩子楼上的壁橱
the point of origin is in
the child's closet upstairs.
是的，我也这样相信
Yes. I believe that too.
亲爱的，你要为了我和为了你
的女儿而坚强点
Honey, you're gonna be strong for me
and for your daughter.
没有了你的信心和对孩子的爱，
我什么都做不了...
I can do absolutely nothing
without your faith in this world...
and your love for the children.
我会的，相信我，我会的
I will.
Believe me, I will.
那你会照我说的做吗？即使违背了
你作为一个人类和基督徒的信仰
And will you do anything I ask,
even if it comes contrary...
to your beliefs as a human being
and a Christian?
是的，我会的
Yes, I promise. Please!
你们都过来好吗?
Would you all come on in?
聚在一起
Gather 'round.
这里没有死亡
There is no death.
只是另一种不同的意识的转换
It is only a transition to
a different sphere of consciousness.
卡罗尔和她身边的东西不同
Carol Anne is not like those
she's with.
她是活生生地生存着的...
She is a living presence...
在他们的精神空间里
in their spiritual earthbound plane.
他们被她的一样东西所吸引...
They are attracted
to the one thing about her...
对他们来说完全不同--
她的生命力
that is different from themselves--
her life force.
非常强大
It is very strong.
它散发出自己的光芒
It gives off
its own illumination.
它意味着生命的光辉...
It is a light that implies life...
爱和家庭的回忆...
and memory of love and home...
和现世的快乐--
and earthly pleasures--
这是他们绝对渴望的...
something they
desperately desire...
但却再也没有的
but can't have anymore.
现在，她最靠近...
Right now, she's the closest thing
to that...
那个可怕的娱乐物...
and that is
a terrible distraction...
有着来自他们的真实光线
from the real light
that has finally come for them.
你听懂我说的吗?
Do you understand me?
这些灵魂，不知什么原因，没有停息...
These souls, who for
whatever reason are not at rest...
也没有意识到他们已经死了
are also not aware
that they have passed on.
他们不是我们所知的意识
They're not part of consciousness
as we know it.
他们永远徘徊于一种梦幻状态...
They linger in
a perpetual dream state...
一个他们永远醒不来的噩梦中
a nightmare from which
they cannot awake.
在七色光中是超度--
Inside the spectral light
is salvation--
隔着窗口看来世
a window to the next plane.
他们必须穿过这层隔膜...
They must pass through
this membrane...
那里有朋友等着引导他们去新的目的地
where friends are waiting
to guide them to new destinies.
卡罗尔必须帮助他们去穿越...
Carol Anne must help them
cross over...
而她只能听见她母亲的声音
and she will only hear
her mother's voice.
现在...
Now...
要坚持住
hold on to yourselves.
还有件事
There's one more thing.
一个可怕的东西在那里和她在一起
A terrible presence
is in there with her.
非常粗暴，非常狂野
So much rage.
So much betrayal.
我以前从没感受过它这样的
I've never sensed
anything like it.
我不知道什么东西盘旋在这个屋子里...
I don't know
what hovers over this house...
但是它有足够的能力打个洞
来到这个世界...
but it was strong enough to punch
a hole into this world...
并带走你们的女儿
and take your daughter
away from you.
它使卡罗尔非常靠近它...
It keeps Carol Anne
very close to it...
远离七色光
and away from the spectral light.
它对她说谎
It lies to her.
它说些只有孩子听得懂的话
It says things
only a child can understand.
它利用她来控制其它幽灵
It has been usin' her
to restrain the others.
对她来说，它只是另一个孩子
To her, it simply is
another child.
对我们来说，它是个野兽
To us, it is the beast.
现在，让我们来找回你女儿
Now let's go get your daughter.
红缎带, 手帕, 网球
Red ribbons,
handkerchiefs, tennis balls.
好的，绳子准备好了
Okay, rope's ready.
- 浴缸里的水呢?
- 我关了，也已经准备好了
- Bathwater?
- I shut it off. It's ready too.
好的，呼叫她吧
All right. Call to her.
卡罗尔, 我是妈妈，
你听得见我吗？
Carol Anne, it's Mommy.
Can you hear me?
卡罗尔,
请对妈妈说hello
Carol Anne,
please tell Mommy hello.
再试试
Try again.
你能对爸爸说声Hello吗?
Can you say hello to Daddy?
我和你爸爸都很想你
Daddy and I miss you so much.
我们都非常想你，
So much. We love you so much.
只要说声Hello
Please, just say hello.
- 她被压抑住了
- 什么?
- She's under restraint.
- What?
- 谁在压抑她?
- 她被许多手臂围住了
- Who's restraining her?
- There are many arms about her.
她认为很安全。你们谁更能威吓到她？
你还是你丈夫？
She thinks it's safe. Who is she more
threatened by, you or your husband?
都不行。史迪夫判定对孩子们的惩罚--
Neither. Steve decides
the punishment the children--
不公平，我从没打过他们--
That's not fair.
I've never laid a hand--
以后再吵，史迪夫,
让卡罗尔回答你们
Fight about it later.
Steven, make Carol Anne answer you.
对她生气
Be cross with her.
我是爸爸
It's Daddy.
对她发怒,否则你将再也见不到她
Be angry with her,
or you'll never see her again.
卡罗尔, 我要你回答我
Carol Anne, I want you
to answer me.
告诉她，如果她不回答你，
你会打她屁股
Tell her if she doesn't answer you,
she'll get a spankin'.
- 我从不打孩子们
- 亲爱的，不要这样，告诉她
- I've never spanked the children.
- Honey, please. Just tell her.
卡罗尔,你快回答你的父母...
Carol Anne,
you answer your parents...
否则我们都会狠狠地打你屁股
or you're gonna get
a real spanking from the both of us!
妈妈! 救我!
Mommy! Help me!
- 她离开了他
- 离开了谁? 她还好吗?
- She's away from him.
- From whom? Is she all right?
达尼, 问问灯的事
Diane, ask about the light.
妈妈，请救我!
Mommy, help me, please!
- 亲爱的，你看见一盏灯了吗?
- 请救救我!
- Honey, do you see a light?
- Help me, please!
妈妈，请救我!
Mommy! Help me!
告诉她，去灯那里
Tell her to go to the light.
他们会跟着她，
他们已经跟着她几个星期了
They'll follow her. They've been
followin' her for weeks.
- 你必须照我说的做!
- 告诉她, 达尼.
- You must do what I say!
- Tell her, Diane.
妈妈，我找不到你!
Mommy, I can't find you!
跑向灯光那里!
用你最快的速度!
Run to the light!
Run as fast as you can!
- 我就在灯光里!
- 不，亲爱的
- I am in the light!
- No, honey.
- 告诉她，你在灯光里
- 不，这是谎言!
- Tell her you are.
- No, it's a lie!
当你的孩子处于困境中，
你可以帮助她选择生或死
You can't choose between life and death
when dealin' with what is in between.
告诉她，否则会太晚了
Tell her before it's too late.
孩子，跑向灯光那里
Run to the light, baby.
- 妈妈就在灯光里
- 告诉她，你在等她
- Mommy is in the light.
- Tell her you're waiting for her.
妈妈正在灯光里等你。
我讨厌这样做
Mommy is waiting for you in the light.
I hate you for this.
现在什么都别想，它知道什么能使你害怕
Now clear your minds.
It knows what scares you.
它从一开始就知道
It has from the very beginning.
不要给它任何帮助。
它已经知道的够多了
Don't give it any help.
It knows too much already.
现在，打开门
Now, open the door.
赖安, 下楼去等待目标!
Ryan, get downstairs
and wait by the target!
给我标记1的网球!
Give me the tennis ball
marked number 1 !
莱斯博士! 是我的笔迹!
它凭空出现了!
Dr. Lesh! It's my handwriting!
It came right out of thin air!
球回来了，是他的笔迹!
The ball came back.
It's his handwriting!
他妈的!
Kiss my ass!
2号球!
Number 2!
把你的手递过来!
Give me your hand!
她就在走廊口!
She's at the mouth
of the corridor!
告诉她停下!
叫她不要走到灯里去!
Tell her to stop!
Tell her not to go into the light!
听我说，不要走进灯里去
Listen to me.
Do not go into the light.
不管你在哪里，停下来。
转过身去
Stop where you are.
Turn away from it.
甚至不要再看灯了
Don't even look at it.
绳子快点!
Hurry with the rope!
扔到灯光里去!
Throw it into the light!
太棒了
Fantastic.
我拿到了!
I got it!
告诉他慢慢拉绳子
Tell him
to take up the slack gently.
拉绳子!
Take up the slack!
帮我把这围在我腰上!
Help me tie this around my waist!
你要干什么?
What are you doing?
我去把她带回来!
I'm goin' in after her!
她不会跟你走的!
我去吧!
She won't come to you!
Let me go!
你以前从没做过!
You've never done this before!
你也没有!
Neither have you!
你是对的，你去
You're right. You go.
不，让我去!
No! Let me!
你不行！这里只有你足够
强壮能拉住绳子
You can't! Who's strong enough
to stay here and hold the rope?
我爱你!
I love you!
不! 到楼下去和赖安一起等...
No! Go downstairs
and wait by Ryan...
听到我命令的时候，用力拉!
and pull only when I say so!
听我的命令
Only when I say.
不要走开!
Don't let go!
不会的!
Never!
来吧
It's coming.
我们怎么知道她找到了她?
How will we know she's got her?
我们什么时候能知道?
When will we know?
横渡，孩子们
Cross over, children.
欢迎你们所有人
All are welcome.
欢迎
All welcome.
走进灯里吧
Go into the light.
你说过，“不要”!
You said, "No" !
灯里有和平和宁静
There is peace and serenity
in the light.
你说过不要走进灯里!
You said don't go into the light!
史迪夫, 还没到时间!
Steven, not yet!
- 她们在这里!
- 她们回来了!
- They're here!
- They're back!
达尼! 不要这样，不要!
Diane! No, please, no!
把她们放进水里!
Get 'em into the water!
- 哦，天啊!
- 不，我要帮你!
- Oh, God!
- No, I'm helping you!
不要担心
Don't worry.
把她们放进水里，她会好的
Get 'em in the water.
She's gonna be all right.
来呀，快呼吸
Come on. Breathe now.
就吸一口气，呼吸
Just take a breath.
Breathe.
呼吸，他妈的，呼吸!
Breathe. Damn it, breathe!
呼吸!
Breathe!
快呀
That's it. Come on.
快呀，呼吸，就是这样，呼吸
Come on. Breathe. Yeah.
That's it. Breathe.
亲爱的
Baby.
甜心
Sweetheart.
宝贝, 我是爸爸
Sweet pea, it's Daddy.
Come on, honey.
快醒醒，小南瓜
Come on, pumpkin.
你好，爸爸
Hi, Daddy.
这房子干净了
This house is clean.
当心
Be careful.
妈，我要去和贾尼斯和布赖恩一起吃饭
Mom, I'm going to dinner
with Janice and Brian.
- 你房间都收拾好了吗?
- 所有的东西，除了床
- Is your room packed up?
- Everything but the bed.
- 我们今晚睡在这里吗?
- 我想不是
- Are we gonna sleep here tonight?
- I guess not.
所以吃完饭，最好马上要布赖恩送你回来
So you better get Brian
to bring you home right after dinner.
爸爸要我们待在假日旅馆 1-74.
Dad wants us to stay
at the Holiday Inn on I-74.
好的，我记住地方里
Oh, yeah.
I remember that place.
你怎么啦?
You what?
你打算怎么处理这个?
Are you gonna do anything
about this?
- 什么?
- 你的新灰发?
- About what?
- Your new gray?
哦，你不喜欢?
Oh. You don't like it?
你不认为这有点庞克的味道?
You don't think
it's kind of punk?
再见，妈妈
Bye, Mom.
亲爱的，我不知道
Honey, I don't know.
好的, 罗比.那东西差点杀了我
Okay, Rob.
That thing almost killed me.
你还好吗?
别伤了你的背
You okay?
Don't hurt your back.
你感觉怎么样?
How you feelin'?
哦，我很好
Oh, I'm good.
我有点宿醉的感觉,
感觉好像睡了好几天...
I feel a little hung over,
like I've been asleep for a few days...
但... 我觉得很好, 史迪夫,
我真的感觉很好
but... I feel good, Steven,
I really do.
她好像什么都不记得了
She doesn't seem
to remember any of it.
哦，真棒的一天
Oh, what a day.
闻上去像含羞草
Smell that mimosa.
你最好割束花带着，我们不再住这里了
You better cut a bouquet and
take it with you. We're not stayin'.
我知道
I know.
我们为此而辛苦工作
We worked so hard for this.
1000个美妙的回忆
A thousand beautiful memories.
我要回办公室，整理点东西
I gotta go to the office, pick up
some stuff, clean up a few things.
我会早点回来
I'll be back early.
我们今晚就离开吗?
We're leaving tonight for sure?
是的
Yeah, we are.
如果孩子们睡着了，就让他们睡到我回来
If the kids get sleepy,
let 'em sleep 'til I get home.
逖格怎么想?
How's Teague taking it?
你知道逖格. 他不会把“去死吧”
当作一种答案
You know Teague. He won't take
"Go to hell" for an answer.
- 你会告诉他什么?
- 我会给他方向
- What will you tell him?
- I'll give him directions.
“...颜色混合后，慢慢从容器中涂到头发上”
"...colored mixture generously
directly from applicator to hair.
让我来玩
- Gently work it through--"
- Let me have that.
我想要回我的卡车!
I want my truck back. Stop!
那是我的卡车!
That's my truck!
给我
Gimme it.
“慢慢用手指使头发吸满
"Gently work it through with fingers
to saturate every strand.
然后用梳子梳理...
Then comb through
with a brush and a comb...
保证每根头发都湿
to be sure entire width
of every hair is wet.
不要太快”
Do not lather."
- 滚出太阳系
- 给我
- Get out of the solar system.
- Gimme it.
- 很晚了，孩子们
- 给我
- It's getting late, guys.
- Gimme it.
- 把它给我
- 给我
- Give it back to me.
- Give it.
- 停下
- 我要洗个盆浴
- Stop it.
- I'm gonna be in the bathtub.
你能接电话吗--
Could you answer the phone--
你能为我接电话吗?
Could you answer the phone
for me, please?
你能自己睡觉吗?
And can you
tuck yourselves in, please?
是的，我们能
Yes, we will.
谢谢你，晚安，甜心
Thank you.
Good night, sweetheart.
- 看看你得到了什么?
- 晚安
- See what you get?
- Good night.
- 晚安, 罗比.
- 晚安, 卡罗尔.
- Good night, Robbie.
- Good night, Carol Anne.
你不是真的!
You're not real!
哦，救命!
Oh! Help!
救命!
Help me!
你不是真的!
You're not real!
让我走!
Let me go!
我讨厌你!
I hate you!
你完了! 我讨厌你!
You're done! I hate you!
我讨厌你!
I hate you!
卡罗尔, 罗比, 快跑!
Carol Anne, Robbie, run!
打开门!
Open the door!
卡罗尔, 罗比, 快跑!
Carol Anne, Robbie, run!
不要碰我的孩子!
Don't touch my babies!
来人啊，救命!
You--
Help me, somebody!
不要
No more.
杜希尔先生!
Mr. Tuthill!
本! 救命!
请救救我!
Ben! Help!
Please help me!
来人救命啊!
Somebody help me! Please!
听着!
那是什么声音?
Listen!
What sort of sound is that?
我要去救他们!
快来!
I've got to get them!
Come on!
- 怎么啦?
- 不要走!
- What's going on?
- Don't go!
- 本帮帮我!
- 不，不要去!
- Please, Ben! Help me!
- No, don't go!
帮我!
Help me!
不要碰我的孩子!
滚开!
Get away from my babies!
Get away!
救命!
Help!
把你的手给我!
Give me your hand!
我够不到你!
I can't reach you!
- 现在抓住你的妹妹!
- 抓住我的手!
- Now grab your sister!
- Take my hand!
快!
Come on!
抓住!
Hold on!
主啊，救救我!
God, help me!
救救我们!
Help us!
你们搬走了公墓，但却留下了尸体，是吗?
You moved the cemetery,
but you left the bodies, didn't you?
你们他妈的混蛋! 搬走了墓石
却留下了尸体
You son of a bitch! You left the bodies
and you only moved the headstones!
你们只搬走了墓石!
You only moved the headstones!
为什么?
Why?
快点，爸爸，快点!
Hurry, Dad, hurry!
- 爸爸，快点!
- 快来
- Dad, hurry!
- Come on.
快点
Hurry.
- 爸爸，快点!
- 史迪夫, 快点!
- Hurry, Dad!
- Come on. Damn it, Steven, hurry!
发生了什么?
What's happening?
- 进车里!
- 那是什么?
- Get in the car!
- What is it?
快开! 爸爸，快开!
Drive away! Daddy, drive away!
史迪夫, 快点!
Steven, hurry!